

E-mail zhs1048@gmail.com

Phone

+8801624748800

Website www.mount-n.com

Address Laksam, Cumilla

ACHIEVEMENTS

2021 | Top Earner Award 2021
LEDP- WDD57
Web Design and Development

• 2020 | Design Contests

Landing Page Design Contests -2021 by HYD

SKILLS





Typography



LANGUAGES

English



ZAHID HASAN

Website & Graphics Designer

ABOUT ME

I am a full time Website and Graphics Designer. Mainly focus on CMS, Fontend Development, User Interface, User Experience, Product Design, Brand Guide or Identity Design, Ads Design etc. My uniqueness in creativity and transparency in my work brings positive sights about me to my clients. All of my clients never remained unsatisfied with my works.

EDUCATION

2018-2022 Noakhali Science And Technology University

BSc in Oceanography, 4th Year 7th Term

2015-2016 | Sonar Bangla Collage, Cumilla

HSC In Science

2015 | Police Line High School, Cumilla

SSC in Science

SOFTWARE

I have a great knowledge on graphics tools and web development tools, also a great skill on M/S Office program.









WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - Now | Web And UI designer

Working as a Web & UI Designer at Mount-n, also a Project Manager.

2020-2021 | Web Designer

Worked as a Web Designer ai ItemAtlas, work for there website for Australia, USA, UK, Germany & India.